and welcome to another installment of
欢迎来到另一期
spring tips in this installment we're
在本期的春季技巧中，我们
going to look at how to do testing and
看看如何进行测试
TDD we look at it in terms of of course
TDD我们当然会看
the features in spring boot so we'll
Spring Boot中的功能，因此我们将
start with a a new project that starts
从一个新的项目开始
out spring that I oh now we're going to
春天，我哦，现在我们要去
follow the three rules of test-driven
遵循测试驱动的三个规则
development which I've seen best
我见过最好的发展
explained by Bob Martin Bob Martin says
鲍勃·马丁解释鲍勃·马丁说
that there are three rules when doing
在做的时候有三个规则
test-driven development so three rules
测试驱动的开发，所以这三个规则
of TDD Bob Martin and you find this can
TDD Bob Martin的作品，您会发现
be a useful blog and that it's the first
成为一个有用的博客，这是第一个
rule is you're not allowed to write any
规则是你不允许写任何东西
production code unless it is to make a
生产代码，除非要制作
failing unit test pass the second rule
单元测试失败通过第二条规则
is that you're not allowed to write any
是不允许你写任何
more of a unit test than is sufficient
单元测试多于足够
to fail and compilation failures are
失败，编译失败是
failures and third and finally you are
失败和第三，最后你是
not allowed to write any more production
不允许再写任何作品
code that is sufficient to pass the one
足以通过一个的代码
failing in test so basically don't move
测试失败，所以基本上不会动
too far ahead right you're gonna keep in
太遥远了，你会留在里面
a cycle keep in a loop as you write a
编写一个循环时保持循环
test you should write the production
测试你应该写生产
code that makes a test pass and then
通过测试的代码，然后
once you've written just enough to make
一旦你写的足够使
that test pass you go back and write
那测试合格你回去写
more tests and you don't write any more
更多测试，您不再写
tests than to make the production code
测试而不是制作生产代码
fail right so it keeps you in a cycle
对的失败，让您保持周期
where you're constantly going back and
你经常回去的地方
forth between production code and test
在生产代码和测试之间
code and test code and production code
代码，测试代码和生产代码
and you know ideally you shouldn't spend
而且你知道理想上你不应该花钱
more than say 30 seconds long on any one
任何人都可以说30秒以上
particular thing right you know you're
对吧，你知道你是
gonna constantly be in this loop the
会一直处于这个循环中
result of doing this the the effect of
这样做的结果
moving to this are many fold first you
首先要移动到这许多折
end up writing software that is testable
最终编写了可测试的软件
right that's the most important
对，这是最重要的
implication of this by writing software
通过编写软件来暗示这一点
is testable you you have to force the
是可测试的，你必须强迫
code to be to be compartmentalized to be
待划分的代码
easily marginalized right the the
容易被边缘化的权利
boundaries the scenes of collaborating
界定合作场景
objects have to be clearly demarcated
必须清楚地标出对象
because that's the only way you can mock
因为那是唯一可以嘲笑的方式
out different layers of the application
遍及应用程序的不同层
right you can mock out these pieces that
对，你可以模拟出这些碎片
you don't care about by substituting
你不在乎取代
dependencies with mocks and so of course
依赖与模拟等等
that lends itself to inversion of
使自己倒置
control and dependency injection the
控制和依赖注入
very basis of all things spring another
万物的基础是另一个
benefit of moving to this architecture
转向这种架构的好处
to this approach of course is that when
这种方法当然是当
you write software
你写软件
you getting a dopamine hit there's a
你得到多巴胺击中
dopamine hit associated with achieving
多巴胺打击与实现
or accomplishing something when you
或完成某件事时
write software that is working and then
编写有效的软件，然后
you write the test it's not very
你写测试不是很好
satisfactory is it it feels like you've
很满意，感觉就像你已经
had to do a chore you went back in with
不得不做一个琐事，你回去
the documentation and you went back and
文档，然后您回去
you wrote the the tests but you already
你写了测试但是你已经
know works and if you're pressed for
知道作品，如果你被迫
time you might very well feel like you
时间，你可能会很想你
can skip that particular step right
可以跳过该特定步骤
because it's already working after all
因为它毕竟已经在工作
that's a that's a bad mindset to get
那是一个不好的心态
into so it's much better to write the
所以最好写成
code or the test first and then write
代码或测试，然后再编写
the satisfying test that satisfy that
满足那个的令人满意的测试
rather then write the satisfying
而不是写令人满意的
production code that's satisfy the test
满足测试的生产代码
so now you've got two for one you've got
所以现在你有两个为一
working code and you've got your
工作代码，您已经拥有了
dopamine hit associated with getting
多巴胺命中与获得
your code to go green when you write
您的代码在编写时变为绿色
code in this way all your code starts
以这种方式编写代码，所有代码开始
with a test so you know you've got good
通过测试，所以你知道自己很好
coverage because you couldn't have
覆盖范围，因为您无法拥有
written a line of pression code without
写了一行压缩代码，没有
having written The Associated test so
已经写了相关测试
you now have a test suite a harness that
您现在有了一个测试套件，可以利用
you can you can trust you can refactor
你可以相信你可以重构
with impunity you know that you've
逍遥法外，你知道你已经
covered everything and so when you make
涵盖了一切，所以当你做
changes you know that the harness will
变化，您知道线束会
capture everything right so you get a
正确捕获所有内容，以便您获得
lot of benefits from this approach I
我从这种方法中获得了很多好处
think it's worth doing we at pivotal of
认为值得我们在关键
course at pivotal labs we do a a lot of
在关键实验室的课程中，我们做了很多
pair programming right pair programming
配对编程正确的配对编程
has a lot of benefits so there's like I
有很多好处，所以就像我
could go on forever but one of the big
可以永远持续下去，但其中之一
benefits is this pair programming
好处是这对编程
approach when you're doing testing we do
当您进行测试时，我们会做
red green refactoring so somebody writes
红绿重构，有人写道
the test to that fail so we write the
测试失败，所以我们写了
test that fails then that the pair
测试失败，然后该对
writes the code that makes set that test
编写设置测试的代码
pass right so you go back and forth and
向右走，所以你来回走
you can send them you can switch roles
您可以发送给他们，也可以切换角色
of course right one person can write the
当然，一个人可以写
production code and the other one
生产代码和另一个
day.the the test and you you get two
天。测试，你得到两个
sides two branes focus on the same
两侧两个黄铜专注于相同
problem and you don't feel like you're
问题，你不觉得自己
stepping in or stepping over each
跨步或跨步
other's feet you're actually writing a
别人的脚，你实际上在写
specification which is the test and then
规范，然后是测试
you're implementing that specification
您正在实施该规范
right so a lot of benefits are moving to
对，所以很多好处正在转移到
this approach I definitely recommend you
我肯定会推荐这种方法
look into it further and we're going to
进一步研究它，我们将
do that today we're gonna look at
今天我们要做的就是看
test-driven development but we're not
测试驱动的开发，但我们不是
going to do we're going to linger too
要做，我们也要流连忘返
long on the on the notion of testing
关于测试的概念由来已久
test driven development were gonna look
测试驱动的开发将看起来
at spring support for testing so
在春季支持测试，所以
let's create a new project as we
让我们在创建一个新项目时
normally do and here it starts a spring
通常会开始春天
that I owe and whilst will call this
我欠的，虽然会叫这个
bootiful testing and when I used to
引导测试以及我以前
bring support from building web
带来来自网络建设的支持
applications we use JPA we use h2 Islam
我们使用JPA的应用程序我们使用h2 Islam
buck and we'll hit generate now I'm not
降压，我们将点击生成，现在我不是
you know it doesn't really matter what
你知道那并不重要
version of spring boot you use all the
春季靴的版本，您使用所有
stuff that doesn't work has been in
不起作用的东西一直在
spring since or rather spring boots
春季以来，或者说 spring boot
since when dot four so we're on firm
从第四点开始，我们就坚定了
ground whatever version we use these
不管我们使用这些版本的版本
days so we'll open up the the release
天，所以我们将打开发布
all right now we have a new application
现在我们有一个新的应用程序
and we could start here but again when I
我们可以从这里开始，但是当我再次
write the tests first so a community
首先写测试，这样一个社区
command here is control shift T in the
这里的命令是
telogen it takes you to the
telogen它带您到
corresponding test in this case we don't
在这种情况下，我们不进行相应的测试
actually want that corresponding test do
其实想要那个对应的测试
we want to start with simple saying that
我们首先要说简单
you know we can build into the system so
你知道我们可以内置到系统中
the first thing we're gonna test is our
我们要测试的第一件事是
basic entity a reservation entity we're
基本实体我们是保留实体
not even going to talk about it in terms
甚至不打算用术语谈论它
of entity you wouldn't talk about it in
的实体，您不会在其中谈论它
terms of the object we're gonna test the
我们要测试的对象的条件
soundness of this entity so when okay a
这个实体的健全性，所以在可以的时候
reservation test and there in will test
预订测试，并会测试
the creation of the object right so a
对象的创建对吧
test public void creation right and I'll
测试公共无效创建权，我将
I will learn to spell having R and in my
我会学会拼写有R
object in my test rather I want to
我想测试中的对象
confirm that when I create an object of
确认当我创建一个对象时
type reservation and I give it some data
类型保留，我给它一些数据
in the constructor that it does the
在构造函数中
right thing so that's create a record of
正确的事情，所以创建了一个记录
that form already our test has failed
表格已经测试失败了
rather so we need to actually create
而是我们需要实际创建
this production class we can hit alt
这个生产课我们可以按alt
enter that'll create it in the
输入将在
corresponding package I want to provide
我要提供的相应包裹
values in the constructor obviously that
构造函数中的值显然是
needs to be done as well now I could
现在我也需要做
create the constructor myself I could
我可以自己创建构造函数
say reservation long L you know and then
说长预定L，你知道然后
string name right but what I want to do
字符串名称正确，但是我想做什么
is actually take a little short shortcut
实际上是采取一些简短的捷径
here I'm going to use the Lombok
在这里，我将使用龙目岛
annotations and you know I'm going to
注释，你知道我要去
take for granted that in this case the
认为在这种情况下
state of my object is the same as the
我的物件的状态与
structure of my alert so all create was
我警报的结构，所以所有创建
to field to your private long ID and
字段到您的私人长ID和
private string reservation name like so
私有字符串保留名称，如下所示
string reservation name a voila so there
字符串保留名称，所以在那里
we are we have two fields by having the
我们有两个领域
at all args constructor and the data
在所有的args构造函数和数据
annotation I get a constructor that will
注解我得到一个构造函数
you know work here and of course now I
你知道在这里工作，当然我现在
can say art I get ID get reservation
可以说我获得身份证获得预订
name etc which lets me write some test
名称等让我写一些测试
so I can say assert equals or get ID and
所以我可以说断言等于或获得ID和
I want to say that it's equal to 1 l
我想说等于1升
right so I'm gonna I'm gonna up cast or
对，所以我要上演
promote correct
促进正确
that that a unboxed integer or long
那是一个未装箱的整数或长整数
rather into a java.lang long there and
而不是到那里的java.lang
i'll sir that it's working so we can run
先生，我正在运行，所以我们可以运行
this test now so let's see run that code
现在进行此测试，让我们看看运行该代码
some teams ever worked good this is one
一些团队曾经表现良好，这是一个
way to do it of course we could do that
当然可以做到的方式
we can use the basic j init methods that
我们可以使用基本的j init方法
have been in jail since you know forever
自从你永远知道以来一直在监狱里
and a day we could also use the assert
有一天我们也可以使用断言
that variance right so asserted that and
该差异权利如此认定，并且
this expects a object of type matcher
这需要一个类型匹配器的对象
now for reasons i don't really
现在由于种种原因，我并不是真的
understand or even care about because
了解甚至关心，因为
it's really gross you're not supposed to
你真的不应该这样
use matcher right you see that matcher
使用匹配器，您会看到匹配器
has this great method that says don't
有这个很棒的方法，说不要
implement matter which of course begs a
实施的事情当然是乞讨
question why did you put that there in
问题你为什么把那放进去
the first place I suspect that given the
我怀疑第一名
availability of default methods in Java
Java中默认方法的可用性
8 these days they wouldn't have made
这8天他们本来不会
that same decision and for other
同样的决定
purposes we just need to extend based
我们只需要扩展的目的
metric so you can create your own custom
指标，以便您可以创建自己的自定义
matress and the nice thing about this
床垫和这件事的好处
approach is that these matters can be
方法是这些事情可以
packaged up you can package them up and
打包，您可以打包它们，
distribute them so now you can reuse
分发它们，以便您现在可以重复使用
complex tests complex assertions and
复杂的测试复杂的断言和
function on be there and for our
功能在那里，为我们
purposes though we're just going to use
目的，尽管我们只是要使用
some pre-built mattress that more or
一些预制的床垫，或者
less mirror to the stuff that we would
更少地反映我们所要的东西
have gotten with basic Dana a certain
有了基本的达娜
asterisk method these are from a project
星号方法，这些来自项目
library called hamcrest and there's a
图书馆叫做hamcrest，有一个
number of different matches here we can
我们可以在这里找到不同的比赛数量
say that we're gonna assert that the ID
说我们要断言这个ID
is equal to 1 L right so there's that
等于1 L对，所以有
now let's run that code again
现在让我们再次运行该代码
okay so that seems to be okay great
好吧，那似乎很好
let's take it one step further we can
让我们更进一步
use a library called a certain J you see
使用一个称为特定J的库
the the the test here has a generic
这里的测试有一个通用的
constraint but otherwise it's not really
约束，但不是真的
you know there's no guidance as to what
你知道关于什么没有指导
is an appropriate matcher to put here
是适合放在这里的匹配器
given the type here given the parameter
给定类型给定参数
on the left so the matcher on the right
在左边所以匹配器在右边
isn't informed necessarily or driven by
不一定被告知或由其驱动
the parameter on the Left where as I've
左边的参数
used the assertions library from assert
使用断言中的断言库
J you can say R get ID is equal to 1 l
J你可以说R get ID等于1 l
right it kind of autocompletes itself
对，它会自动完成
and so I prefer that right get
所以我更喜欢正确的选择
reservation name see that works but I
保留名称看到的作品，但我
can see that it also says it's not blank
可以看到它还说它不是空白
and I can say that is equal to Jane so I
我可以说那等于简，所以我
get this a very very convenient sort of
得到这个非常非常方便的
type safe matching functionally this
在功能上键入安全匹配
test functionality and the test
测试功能和测试
basically writes itself let's break the
基本上写自己让我们打破
test here let's say that it's equal to
在这里测试，让我们说它等于
Janet and see what happens right the
珍妮特，看看会发生什么
error message is very useful here right
错误消息在这里非常有用
so you get all that functionality very
这样您就可以获得所有功能
quickly you know all that is nice let's
很快，您就知道一切都很好，让我们
close this now I have just use the
现在关闭它，我只是使用
assertions library that's fine but it's
断言库很好，但是
also interesting that there's a BDD
也很有趣，有一个BDD
assertions class in a certain day which
某天的断言类
gives you basically the same
给你基本相同
functionality but with a then keyword so
功能，但带有then关键字，因此
you can say given when then using the BD
您可以说在使用BD时给出了
style of testing and that's worth your
测试风格，这值得您
consideration as well if you're doing
如果您正在做的话也要考虑
BDD which you should be I mean there's a
BDD，你应该是我的意思是有一个
use case for that right so I never say
用例的权利，所以我永远不会说
never but for our purposes I think it
从来没有，但出于我们的目的，我认为
surprises delay things as they are here
惊喜拖延了他们在这里的事情
now the next thing that we're gonna want
现在我们想要的下一件事
to test is the the JPA mapping right so
要测试的是JPA映射，所以
we've got a class but it's not entity we
我们有一堂课，但不是实体，
just know that structurally it'll do the
只是知道从结构上讲
right thing when I give it a constructor
当我给它一个构造函数时是对的
argument it'll pop out give it a given
参数会弹出给定
an invocation to an accessor right so
对访问器的调用是正确的
that that's working we can say a
那行得通，我们可以说一个
reservation JPA test
预约JPA测试
okay and there's this and we can say
好的，有这个，我们可以说
test public void and what we're going to
测试公众空白以及我们将要做什么
do is test the mapping right so I want
我要做的就是测试映射，所以我想要
to test the mapping here of the GOP
在这里测试GOP的映射
entity when it interacts with the Jaypee
与Jaypee互动时的实体
and any
和任何
manager well I could you know mock or I
经理好，我可以知道模拟还是我
could configure all of JPA and the data
可以配置所有的JPA和数据
source and all that stuff but I forgot
来源和所有这些东西，但我忘了
spring and spring already knows about
春天和春天已经知道
all that wiring so why would I recreate
所有的布线，所以我为什么要重新创建
that so I can actually use the at run
这样我就可以实际使用
with spring runner class and the spring
与春季跑步者班和春季
runner is a is a test runner that we
赛跑者是一个测试赛跑者，我们
provide in in spring Boone and in spring
在春季提供布恩和春季
framework and it's a test runner that is
框架，它是一个测试运行器
you know it's a mechanism that Gena
你知道这是Gena的一种机制
itself exposes right this is a thing
本身就暴露这件事
that's from j-unit which you can use to
这是从j-unit可以用来
tell spring - you can tell Gina - to
告诉春天-你可以告诉吉娜-
involve spring in the execution of your
让春天参与您的执行
tests and to make available
测试并提供
collaborating objects and so on so
协作对象等等
that's very very convenient you need to
这非常方便，您需要
give this more information that way this
通过这种方式提供更多信息
will say activate the machinery required
会说激活所需的机器
to run spring but you know what would a
跑春天，但你知道会发生什么
plication context what configuration
情境上下文什么配置
class right a lots of things here they
他们在这里上了很多东西
are required there are a lot of things
需要很多东西
that are required beyond the recognition
无法识别的要求
that we're going to be involving spring
我们将要参与春天
somehow so we could say at spring boot
以某种方式让我们可以在春季启动时说
test and you know there's a classes
测试，你知道有一个课程
parameter or an attribute that is
参数或属性是
expecting the configuration class that
期望配置类
we want to run we could certainly do
我们想跑步，我们当然可以做
that that's certainly one option the
那当然是一种选择
problem with this of course is that the
这个问题当然是
the default behavior of the spring boot
弹簧靴的默认行为
test annotation is to load the entire
测试注解是加载整个
application context and all we're trying
应用程序上下文以及我们正在尝试的一切
to do is to test our interaction with
要做的是测试我们与
JPA just the entitymanager mapping right
JPA只是entitymanager映射的权利
just the interaction between the energy
只是能量之间的相互作用
manager and the annotations on my entity
经理和我的实体上的注释
so I don't want to startup Tomcat just
所以我不想只启动Tomcat
to test that I'd much prefer to instead
测试我更愿意代替
start up a slice of the of the
开始的
application context related to
与以下内容相关的应用程序上下文
persistence and JPA and run that and
持久性和JPA并运行
then in isolation test the things there
然后隔离测试那里的东西
that we care about and then leave out
我们关心的，然后省去
the rest right and that was easier to do
其余的权利，那更容易做到
before in the world of manual
之前的手册世界
configuration of everything with you
与您一起配置一切
know different spring application
了解不同的弹簧应用
context xml's and configuration classes
上下文xml和配置类
you could certainly slice and dice your
你当然可以切成薄片
application in terms of layers and that
在层次上的应用
was a little bit easier to do because
有点容易做，因为
they'd have multiple configuration files
他们将有多个配置文件
and you could
你可以
in your tests instantiate just one
在您的测试中仅实例化一个
application context XML and ignore the
应用程序上下文XML并忽略
rest that was certainly an option I
休息那当然是我的选择
don't want to go back to that though I
虽然我不想回到那个
much rather let spring boot write the
宁可让spring boot编写
configuration for me I'm very happy with
我很满意的配置
that and what what little is left i I
那，我还剩下什么
test myself that said I don't want to
测试自己，说我不想
run the whole application just to test a
运行整个应用程序只是为了测试
piece of functionality so spring boot
功能的一部分，因此启动了春季
1.4 has this concept of a test slice so
1.4具有测试切片的概念，因此
instead of using at spring boot test
而不是在春季启动测试中使用
which is like it's it's a slice of the
就像这是其中的一部分
whole it's the slice that is equal to
整体上等于
the whole pie basically instead of using
整个馅饼基本上而不是使用
that I'm going to use a data JPA test
我将要使用数据JPA测试
class and here that can provide a number
类，在这里可以提供一个数字
of different things but what this is
不同的东西，但这是什么
going to say is first of all it's gonna
首先要说的是
do it's going to do three things it's
要做这三件事
gonna register it's going to remove the
要注册它将删除
outer configuration that is there by
外部配置
default it's going to basically set to
默认情况下，它将基本上设置为
zero all the configuration classes that
将所有的配置类归零
spring but would normally run then it's
春天，但通常会运行然后
going to provide some configuration
将提供一些配置
classes that should be run then it's
应该运行的类，然后
going to contribute things that we would
将贡献我们将要做的事情
need to effectively test this kind of
需要有效地测试这种
stuff so including stuff that you
东西，包括你的东西
wouldn't otherwise get in the auto
否则不会进入汽车
configuration for the production code
生产代码的配置
right this is stuff that is valuable
对，这是有价值的东西
only in a test context and also part of
仅在测试环境中并且也是
that it'll set some defaults it'll set
它会设置一些默认值
for example that that the test methods
例如那个测试方法
here are transactional right so you can
这是交易权，因此您可以
see here that there's a lot of a lot of
看到这里有很多
stuff happening here it says this is
这里发生的事情说这是
going to be it's going to override auto
将要覆盖自动
configuration it's going to exclude
配置将要排除
certain classes from the application
应用程序中的某些类
context we're telling spring don't
我们告诉春天的背景不要
bother with certain types just ignore
打扰某些类型只是忽略
them pretend that they aren't registered
他们假装他们没有注册
we don't want them in this code base
我们不希望他们在此代码库中
anyway
无论如何
and we're going to tell it to auto
我们要告诉它自动
configure certain things and these
配置某些东西，这些
annotations also have attributes that
注释还具有以下属性
are mapped sometimes to properties so
有时会映射到属性，因此
for example let's see going back here
例如让我们看看回到这里
there we go we can see that the cache
我们去那里，我们可以看到缓存
provider attribute for the auto
自动的提供者属性
configure cache is mapped to the spring
配置缓存映射到spring
boot property file you know value called
您知道值称为的启动属性文件
spring that cache that type so if you in
弹簧缓存该类型，因此如果您在
your test folder have an application
您的测试文件夹有一个应用程序
that yeah mall or application are
是的购物中心或应用程序是
properties that has spring that cache
具有弹簧缓存的属性
that type equals whatever it'll be set
该类型等于将要设置的类型
on this annotation and
在这个注释上
used to inform the behavior of this test
用于告知此测试的行为
only in the test code right so you get a
仅在测试代码中正确，这样您就可以
lot of be a lot of nice benefits here um
这里很多很多好处
you'll also notice that we have this we
您还会注意到我们有这个
looked at this before we had this
在我们有这个之前看了这个
override Auto configuration this tells
覆盖自动配置，这告诉
spring spring boot rather that oh and by
春天春天引导而不是哦和
the way we also have other properties
我们还有其他属性的方式
here I just saw that spring JPSO shows
在这里，我刚刚看到春天的JPSO节目
equal is equal to true right you could
等于等于您可以的真实权利
override that but it's equal to true by
覆盖它，但等于true
default so you you'll see later on when
默认设置，因此稍后您会看到
we use jpay that it's kind of show us a
我们使用jpay可以向我们展示
DDL that's used to create the entities
用于创建实体的DDL
um one thing that's nice about this
嗯，这件事很好
overwriting Auto configuration is that
覆盖自动配置是
we're telling spring to set you know to
我们告诉春天让你知道
remove all the auto configuration and
删除所有自动配置并
then let us recreate from zero the
然后让我们从零开始重新创建
configuration required to do JPA and to
执行JPA所需的配置
test in that world we can we can provide
在那个世界中测试我们可以提供
our own auto configuration as well so we
我们自己的自动配置
can say you know spring that factory's
可以说你知道春天工厂的
text file in the meta introductory we
元介绍中的文本文件
can create our own text file that has
可以创建我们自己的文本文件
the name of this annotation org spring
该批注的名称org spring
frame boot test Orem JPA did it APA test
框架启动测试Orem JPA进行了APA测试
equals and then our own auto
等于然后我们自己的汽车
configurations so that whenever we use
配置，以便每当我们使用
day to day pay test our own auto
日常支付测试我们自己的汽车
configurations are involved as well
以及配置
going beyond what's happening here and
超越这里发生的事情
this whole mechanism by the way of
整个机制的方式
course is completely reusable you can
当然可以完全重用
create your own tests Isis perhaps
创建自己的测试Isis也许
you've got some aspect of the
你有一些方面
application that should be tested in
应在以下位置进行测试的应用程序
isolation independent of the default
独立于默认值的隔离
configurations in spring boot and you
Spring Boot中的配置和你
can absolutely do that you can package
绝对可以做到，你可以打包
it up as a test slice annotation like
像测试切片注解一样
this and and then stupid that and that
这个，然后愚蠢的那个，那个
way there's a go to usable mechanism for
一种可行的机制
instantiating just the bits that you
仅实例化您的位
care about when your test let's see what
关心什么时候测试让我们看看
else do we care about here huh we have
否则我们在这里关心吗
excluded we have the in Harrison we've
排除了我们在哈里森
got the auto configuration ah what do we
得到了自动配置啊我们该怎么办
have Auto configure in here this stuff
在这里有自动配置
makes a lot of sense this is just basic
很有意义，这只是基础
spring data GPA of course as well that's
春季数据GPA当然也是
gonna work as we expect here's the cash
会像我们期望的那样工作，这是现金
support but this is gonna create a test
支持，但这将创建一个测试
database so in my build in my build I
数据库，所以在我的构建中
have a spring boot starter data JPA and
有一个弹簧启动启动器数据JPA和
it has a h2 database here to work with
它在这里有一个H2数据库
right this is a default
对，这是默认设置
convenience you see me use this a lot in
方便，你看我经常用
various spring boot videos I use h2
我使用h2的各种 spring boot 视频
because it's embedded it's in memory
因为它嵌入在内存中
it's
它的
to stand it up I don't have to configure
站起来，我不需要配置
a data source I don't have to have
我不需要的数据源
anything running my local machine which
任何运行我的本地计算机的东西
by extension means that you don't either
通过扩展意味着您不会
if you want to play with the code but
如果你想玩代码，但是
the the underlying assumption of course
当然的基本假设
always is that you're probably not gonna
永远是你可能不会
use that in production you're gonna go
在生产中使用它，你会去
to application of properties and say
申请财产并说
spring that data source that password a
弹出该密码的数据源
user name or URL or whatever and point
用户名或URL或其他任何内容
it to something real like a my sequel or
就像我的续集或
Postgres or Oracle or whatever right
Postgres或Oracle或其他权利
sequel server you know anything these
续集服务器，您知道这些
days
天
and you can certainly do that and you
你当然可以做到，你
probably will all right that said that's
可能会说那是
not gonna be what you test against is it
不会成为您要测试的对象
I don't expect you to test your your
我不希望您测试您的
application against your production
针对您的生产的应用
Oracle database that would be crazy so
Oracle数据库太疯狂了，所以
instead you're gonna want to mock out or
相反，您将要模拟或
at least point to a different data
至少指向不同的数据
source and you can do that by
来源，您可以通过
overwriting the properties but that gets
覆盖属性，但得到
to be very tedious you have to now
要非常乏味，您必须现在
involve you know your Oracle a Oracle
让您知道您的甲骨文
installation somewhere just to run your
在某处安装只是为了运行您的
unit tests and that's even more grading
单元测试，而且评分更高
because we don't care about oral color
因为我们不在乎口腔颜色
at this point all we're trying to prove
在这一点上，我们正在尝试证明
is that when I map my entity that jpay
是当我映射我的实体时，jpay
knows to knows what to do with it that's
知道要怎么做
it that's all we're trying to prove here
这就是我们要在这里证明的全部
we don't need the database for that you
我们不需要您的数据库
know we we want some database we want
知道我们想要一些我们想要的数据库
something there but really we're just
那里有东西，但实际上我们只是
trying to prove it we've got the right
试图证明它是正确的
mapping annotations in place so that's a
将注解映射到位，这是一个
layer below us that we don't care about
我们不在乎的下面的一层
and I want to mock it out already
我已经想把它嘲笑了
someone I'm not care about and that's
我不在乎的人
what this the annotation is gonna do
注释将要做什么
it's going to create a in-memory h2
它会创建一个内存中的h2
database for us even though right now my
即使现在我的数据库
application is using h2 I could say use
应用程序正在使用H2我可以说使用
post quiz this would still create an
发布测验，这仍然会创建一个
in-memory h2 database for us in the test
测试中为我们提供的内存h2数据库
context so my my reads and writes are
上下文，所以我的读写是
all to this sort of in-memory ephemeral
都是这种短暂的记忆
database it makes it really really quick
数据库，它真的非常快
we're also going to auto configure a
我们还将自动配置一个
test entity manager if you've ever dealt
测试实体经理（如果您曾经交易过）
with a low-level JPA persistence context
具有低级JPA持久性上下文
annotated any manager then you know that
给任何经理加注释，那么你知道
any manager is a generic friendly
任何经理都是通用友善的
version of the hibernate session
休眠会话的版本
basically and it's very low-level and if
基本上，这是非常低级的，如果
we're trying to do things with what's
我们正在尝试用什么做事
testing then the the the use cases the
然后测试用例
patterns in testing are going to be
测试中的模式将是
different from the the interactions you
与您的互动不同
might expect when you write production
编写作品时可能会期望
code using the entity manager so this
使用实体管理器的代码
creates a new object it contributes a
创建一个新对象，它有助于
new object that's useful only in the
仅在
context of testing and that object is
测试的上下文，该对象是
called guess what test enemymanager
叫猜测什么测试敌人经理
and it provides some convenient
它提供了一些方便
so we'll take advantage of that as well
所以我们也会利用它
so here we go we better mapping I'm
所以在这里，我们可以更好地映射
gonna auto wire the test entitymanager
将自动连接测试实体经理
all right te M AR and we're going to use
好的，我们将使用
that test any manager willing to say
测试任何经理愿意说的
this TEM and when we call persist flush
这个TEM以及当我们称为持久冲洗时
and find so this is going to be a you
找到所以这将是你
know three four it's gonna write it's
知道它要写三四个
gonna write the record to our in-memory
要将记录写到我们的内存中
database to test you know test database
数据库测试你知道测试数据库
that we have it's going to flush the
我们有它要冲洗
session and then it's going to retrieve
会话，然后它将检索
the record by its ID all in one fell
通过其ID的记录合而为一
swoop so we can prove exactly what we're
猛扑，所以我们可以证明我们到底是什么
trying to prove which is that given a
试图证明给定一个
new reservation oops
新预订哦
of the following form null and chain
以下形式的null和链
that we get back a record that we expect
我们得到了我们期望的记录
so there's Jane we're gonna say
所以有珍妮，我们要说
assertions dot Jane dot get reservation
断言点简点得到保留
name that is equal to Jane good and I'm
这个名字等于简·古德，我是
gonna say get ID is not know right so
会说获得身份证不知道是对的
there's that as well
还有那个
so we've got these two different methods
所以我们有这两种不同的方法
we were going to say that research
我们要说的是研究
reservation name is equal to name to
保留名等于
Jean and the ID is gonna be not know we
吉恩（Jean）和身份证将不知道我们
also want to say that the ID should be
也想说ID应该是
greater than for example one zero right
例如大于一零
we don't it's that's a truism for a
我们不是，这是不言而喻的
primary key here all right so let's see
这里的主键好吧，让我们看看
what that code looks like let's run that
该代码看起来像什么，让我们运行它
code and of course that failed because
代码，当然失败了，因为
we're testing the wrong thing first all
我们首先要测试错误的东西
I forgot to undo the old tests I'm glad
我忘了撤消旧测试我很高兴
we ran that so we can fix it so let's
我们运行了它，所以我们可以修复它，所以让我们
see reservation
查看预订
jp8 test and that's this one reservation
jp8测试，这是一个保留
test we broke this earlier just to prove
测试我们更早打破了这个只是为了证明
what would happen and I forgot to
会发生什么，我忘了
restore it
恢复它
all right that's this and now the
好吧，这就是现在
mapping we're gonna test by running it
映射我们将通过运行它进行测试
instead good now that's fine now we run
相反，现在好了，现在我们运行
this which is the mapping test okay so
这是映射测试好吗
at that broke predictably it's saying
可以预见的是，
that we have an unknown entity that's
我们有一个未知的实体
fair enough so let's go back to our
足够公平，让我们回到我们的
entity and bring in the Jaypee into the
实体并将Jaypee带入
annotation and we can run that same code
注释，我们可以运行相同的代码
again mapping now breaks a different way
再次映射现在打破了另一种方式
I would expect yep no identifiers
我希望没有标识符
specified for the entity so at ID at
为实体指定，因此ID为
generated value right there we are so
产生的价值就在这里
let's run this one more time all right
让我们再运行一​​次
so that seems to be good and green
所以看起来很好而且绿色
moving up let's now test the repository
现在让我们测试存储库
so we're gonna say reservation
所以我们要说预订
repository test and what we're trying to
存储库测试以及我们正在尝试的
do here is to prove that our custom
这样做是为了证明我们的习惯
Feiner method works right we're not
Feiner方法行得通，我们不是
going to test the repository itself we
要测试存储库本身，我们
know that spring data works just fine I
知道弹簧数据可以正常工作
don't need to prove that the final
不需要证明最终
method and save method and all that
方法和保存方法以及所有这些
stuff work as expected that's been
东西按预期工作
tested time and time again by
一次又一次地测试
innumerable many other people or we
许多其他人或我们
don't have to worry about that that's
不必担心那是
the benefit of building a framework but
建立框架的好处，但是
if we customize the repository and
如果我们自定义存储库，
provide custom finder methods it can be
提供可以的自定义查找器方法
useful to validate that that's working
有助于验证其是否有效
as we expect it to so let's do the same
正如我们期望的那样，让我们​​做同样的事情
thing as we did before public void we're
就像我们在公共场合无效之前所做的一样
going to test define by reservation name
要测试通过预订名称定义
method and this of course you is the
方法，这当然是您的
spring runner so sorry as run with
春季跑步者，很抱歉与
spring runner dot class and that'll be
春天赛跑者点类，那将是
of course a data jjjp
当然是数据jjjp
test that we aren't good and we're going
测试我们不好，我们要去
to inject our reservation repository all
注入我们所有的预订库
right here we are so that repository
在这里，我们就是这样的仓库
doesn't exist of course so we'll create
当然不存在，所以我们将创建
that
那
otherwise we have a failing test okay
否则我们的测试会失败
and we're gonna use the repository when
我们将在以下情况下使用存储库
I say this not repository us save of
我说这不是我们保存的资料库
course we can't save a new record until
当然，我们要等到新记录才能保存
we have the save method so we're already
我们有save方法，所以我们已经
at our first failing test let's fix that
在我们第一次失败的测试中，让我们修复一下
all right I'll then to recreate this
好吧，我会重新创建这个
method we could do that but of course we
方法我们可以做到，但是我们当然
we both know that a spring data will do
我们都知道弹簧数据可以
that for us so we're gonna say @jp a
对于我们来说，所以我们要说@jp a
repository reservation managing entities
仓库预订管理实体
it took long there we are
我们在那里花了很长时间
and that'll give us a saved record in
这将给我们保存的记录
the database and we should be able to
数据库，我们应该能够
based on that use our repository to find
基于此，使用我们的存储库查找
by reservation name passing in Jane and
通过在简和中传递的预订名称
of course this method doesn't exist and
当然这种方法不存在，
that's a far more problematic one we
那是我们要解决的问题
have to actually implement that one
必须实际实施
that's our that's the thing that's gonna
那是我们的，那将是
be under test right so here we are
在测试中，所以我们在这里
reservation string there we are named
保留字符串，我们被命名为
airway there's a custom finder method
气道有自定义查找器方法
our test now should we turn a collection
现在我们应该测试我们是否应该收集
of you know by reservation name results
你们知道通过预订名称结果
we can say assertions that by
我们可以说断言
reservation name that size is equal to 1
保留名称，其大小等于1
right remember we're using a test
正确的记住我们正在使用测试
database so there's no more than one
数据库，所以不超过一个
record in the database and we want to
记录在数据库中，我们想要
say that the iterator dot next dot get
说迭​​代器点下一个点得到
ID is greater than 0 and we're going to
ID大于0，我们将
recreate the iterator so we'll get the
重新创建迭代器，以便我们获得
same record back again and we're gonna
相同的记录又回来了，我们要
get now the reservation name I'm going
现在得到我要去的预订名称
to say that that is equal to Jane all
说等于简·所有
right so let's now try running that one
好的，让我们现在尝试运行那个
find reservation name
查找预订名称
good stuff all right so we now have a
好东西好，所以我们现在有一个
test that proves that our interaction
测试证明我们的互动
with the repositories working as
仓库作为
expected we can see by the way of course
希望我们可以顺便看到
the DDL I mentioned that that would
我提到的DDL
happen earlier we can see the DDL
发生得更早，我们可以看到DDL
reflect on the console here
在这里反映在控制台上
and so we've tested in there now let's
因此，我们现在已经在那里进行了测试
build a weapon API let's test the rest a
建立武器API，让我们测试其余的
pack that we're gonna build first of
我们首先要制造的包装
course I want to say reservation rest
我当然要说休息
controller test and here instead of
控制器测试，这里代替
using the test life supporting data
使用寿命支持数据
access we're going to use the web MVC
访问，我们将使用Web MVC
test and test slice so I'm going to use
测试和测试切片，所以我要使用
that and the spring runner dot class all
那和春季赛跑者圆点班
right
对
and the at web MVC test couldn't figures
而且at web MVC测试无法计算
for us the cash support the web MVC
对我们来说，现金支持Web MVC
support mock NB c-- and exclude certain
支持模拟NB c--并排除某些
objects that we don't care about
我们不在乎的对象
including those by the way related to
包括那些与
persistence so this isn't the right tier
持久性，所以这不是正确的层
the test persistence logic we've already
我们已经存在的测试持久性逻辑
done that so we want to take that for
做到这一点，所以我们想
granted so we're going to take advantage
理所当然，所以我们要利用
of the pre-configured mock NB C client
预先配置的模拟NB C客户端
right that's what's been configured for
正确的就是为此配置的
us and I'm gonna create a new test
我们和我要创建一个新测试
public void get reservation so we're
公共无效得到预订，所以我们
going to prove that given a request that
将证明给定一个要求
we get the right response so mark mu C
我们得到正确的回应，所以标记亩C
perform Muk mu C result mattress dot
执行Muk mu C结果床垫点
status that is okay so I'm sorry we have
状态还可以，对不起，我们有
to do this correctly result request
正确执行此结果请求
builders that get reservations there we
在那得到预订的建筑商
go and expect that it's okay
去期待没事
right now we add the exception there
现在我们在这里添加例外
there's our simplest test
这是我们最简单的测试
that's a as little as I can write to
那是我可以写的
fail all right now the amok mu C client
现在全部失败amok mu C客户
here is a sort of an engineered
这是一种工程
agreement between the rest framework the
其余框架之间的协议
framework errs spring MVC of course and
框架错误当然是MVC和
the the the the test code here we're not
测试代码在这里我们不是
actually creating real HTTP calls
实际创建真正的HTTP调用
there's no socket open here with HTTP
这里没有使用HTTP打开的套接字
payloads going across the wire what's
穿过电线的有效载荷是什么
happening is we're making requests
发生的是我们正在提出要求
through the service from the client but
通过客户的服务，但是
the client is talking to spring NB C
客户正在与Spring NB C交谈
itself not
本身不是
- Tomcat or something like Tomcat we're
-Tomcat或类似Tomcat之类的东西
not there's no server socket listening
没有服务器套接字监听
for requests so this is going straight
要求，所以这是直的
to spring MVC spring MVC is processing
弹簧MVC弹簧MVC正在处理
the request as though or an actual
好像是实际的请求
request from the web it's going through
来自网络的请求
all of the processing phases going
所有处理阶段都在进行
through the the HTTP messaging
通过HTTP消息传递
translation and the message converters
翻译和消息转换器
the validation the you know all that
验证您知道的一切
stuff to do with processing of a request
与处理请求有关的东西
after this Tomcat has turned it into a
在这个Tomcat把它变成一个
httpservletrequest right all that stuff
httpservlet请求正确的所有东西
is being done for us just as though we
为我们所做的就像我们
had actually issued the request but the
实际上已经发出了请求，但是
benefit we're not starting up Tomcat
好处是我们没有启动Tomcat
because we don't care about Tomcat we
因为我们不在乎Tomcat
know Tomcat works so let's let's get
知道Tomcat可以工作，所以让我们开始吧
this basic test to work let's go ahead
这个基本的测试工作让我们继续
and go to our reservation controller
然后去我们的预订控制器
again very convenient we can go here and
再次非常方便，我们可以去这里
reservation rest control the reservation
预约休息控制预约
rest controller and we'll say at test ok
休息控制器，我们会说确定
oh sorry we're not going to say at get
哦，对不起，我们不会在get说
mapping and it's gonna be a four slash
映射，它将是四个斜线
reservations and point and all we're
保留和观点，我们所有
gonna do is return an empty array list
要做的是返回一个空数组列表
right so collections dot empty and we'll
正确，因此收藏集的内容为空，我们将
say at rest controller there we are so
说休息控制器，我们是如此
we'll go back to our test here and run
我们将回到这里进行测试并运行
this again
再来一次
good that passed let's do something more
好了，让我们做更多的事情
substantial we'll say also that we
充实的我们也会说我们
expect the content the content type to
期望内容类型的内容
be equal to application JSON like so we
等于像这样的应用程序JSON，所以我们
start this all right that seems to be
开始这似乎是好的
working good let's now do something
工作良好，让我们现在做点什么
that's just a bit more substantial than
只是比
that we'll actually poke at the result
我们实际上会戳结果
that comes back so mark MVC result mat
回来，所以标记MVC结果垫
shirts dot JSON path and we're going to
衬衫点JSON路径，我们将
say at that zero dot ID is going to be
说零点ID将是
equal to one l and we're gonna say that
等于一升，我们要说
the reservation name again I'm writing
我再次写的预订名称
two tests instead of one I shouldn't do
两项测试而不是一项，我不应该做
that it's going to be equal to Jane and
它将等于简和
we'll run this again and that should
我们将再次运行它，应该
fail substantially right all right so we
好吧，基本上失败吧，所以我们
know that there is no value at that JSON
知道那个JSON没有价值
path expression here we're using the J
路径表达式，这里我们使用的是J
way
方式
jason path match to write sets that
杰森路径匹配来写集
supporter for us we don't have to import
我们的支持者，我们不必导入
anything that just works and we need to
任何有效的方法，我们需要
actually configure we need to respond
实际配置我们需要响应
with data in the response and we can do
在响应中添加数据，我们可以
that of course by injecting the
当然可以通过注入
repository so it's a private final
资料库，所以这是私人决赛
reservation repository injecting that
预订存储库注入
into the constructor and then here we'll
进入构造函数，然后在这里我们将
say return this type reservation
说返回此类型的保留
repository at find all now if I go back
如果我回去，现在查找全部内容
to this test what do you think is gonna
这次测验你认为会怎样
happen it's not gonna work we know that
碰巧，这行不通，我们知道
right All Right see that it says no such
对，没错，它说没有
beam definition exception no qualifying
光束定义异常无合格
being of type comm bootiful testing
进行通讯启动测试
reservation for paws are available
可以预订爪子
that's because it's been excluded from
那是因为它被排除在外
the application context and that's by
应用程序上下文
design the last thing that we want to
设计我们想要的最后一件事
test is our database layer we're not
测试是我们的数据库层，我们不是
trying to test that we know that that
试图测试我们知道
works we've already done an extensive
我们已经做了大量的工作
amount of testing and that layer and
测试量以及该层和
below it to prove that that works so
在它下面证明这行得通
instead what we need to do is to mock
相反，我们需要做的是模拟
out the reservation repository have to
出预订库必须
tell our risk controller to use the
告诉我们的风险控制者使用
reservation repository but we're gonna
预订资料库，但我们要
give it a a fake version of that object
给它一个该对象的伪造版本
you know we know that's an interface so
你知道我们知道这是一个界面
we can provide any implementation that
我们可以提供任何实现
we want and this would be possible you
我们想要，这将是可能的
could contribute your own custom
可以贡献自己的风俗
configuration class right I could say
我可以说配置类对
you know
你懂
let me see can I do that I can say uh I
让我看看我能不能说我
guess I can't I hope if you're using
猜猜我不能希望你在用
spring boot test you can provide own
您可以提供自己的Spring Boot测试
custom configuration class I think you
自定义配置类，我想你
can actually say just my config and make
实际上可以说我的配置并
this a configuration class and then
这是一个配置类，然后
provide your own being of type of
提供你自己的类型
reservation repository that's I guess
我猜是保留库
that's an option let's see what happens
这是一个选择，让我们看看会发生什么
if we do that right so mockito dot mock
如果我们做对了，那么模仿点模拟
reservation repository at class and this
班级预订资料库
will give you a response and what we're
会给您答复以及我们的
gonna say mockito dot dot when mock dot
当模拟点时要说模拟点
find all dot then return raise dot pass
找到所有点然后返回提高点通过
list new reservation and it'll be one l
列出新的预订，它将是一个l
and Jane right I think that's I think
和简，我认为那是我的想法
that'll work so let's see return mock so
那会起作用的，所以让我们看一下返回模拟
that usually works I know you can do
通常可以正常工作，我知道你可以做到
something like that with the spring loot
春天的战利品
test framework support does that work
测试框架支持可以正常工作
all right the content-type has not been
好吧，内容类型还没有
set so we're losing for different
设置，所以我们为不同而输
reasons let's try fixing the risk
原因让我们尝试解决风险
controller here produces media type
控制器在这里产生媒体类型
application JSON utf-8 value okay
应用程序JSON utf-8值还可以
content type is not set well it doesn't
内容类型设置不正确
make sense I'll bet that this is to do
我敢打赌这是要做的
with my clumsy mocking of the object
我笨拙地嘲笑对象
here and that's okay that's actually
在这里，没关系，实际上
just fine because this isn't the right
很好，因为这不合适
way to solve it anyway is my point what
解决问题的方法是我的意思是什么
we need to do is to mark out that object
我们需要做的是标记该对象
and replace it with a mock bean right so
并用一个模拟豆替换它，这样
we could attempt to carve it out
我们可以尝试将其雕刻出来
ourselves and provide a custom
自己，并提供一个习惯
configuration class and that that as you
配置类以及您
see it it's I'm not sure if even
看到它是我不确定
possible in this particular
在这方面可能
configuration then either way it's the
配置然后无论哪种方式
wrong way to do it instead we can take
错误的方式来代替我们可以采取
advantage of an object called mark bean
称为标记豆的对象的优势
orientation rather called mock bean what
定位而不是模拟豆什么
this does is it provides you with a it's
这是它为您提供了一个
hell spring that this type should be
地狱春天，这种类型应该是
contribute to the application context if
有助于应用程序上下文
it doesn't exist and if it does exist it
它不存在，如果确实存在
should be replaced with this mock object
应该用这个模拟对象代替
so here going to contribute a bean of
所以这里要贡献一个
type reservation repository that's gonna
输入将要保留的预订存储库
be a mock and house I'm not going to be
做一个模拟和房子我不会
created well it's gonna use mockito just
创建得很好，它将只使用mockito
like I tried to do a minute ago using
就像我在一分钟前尝试使用
that custom clumsy configuration class
该自定义笨拙的配置类
this mock well you know now when spring
你现在春天知道的这个模拟游戏
starts up it's gonna inject this
启动它会注入这个
reservation repository this will work
预订存储库将起作用
it'll get as far as a constructor this
它将达到构造函数的范围
pointer will be to a mock object and
指针将指向模拟对象，并且
everything will be will be just fine
一切都会好起来的
until we get to this line we're trying
直到我们到达这一行，我们正在尝试
return the data from the final method
从最终方法返回数据
that's not gonna work for of course
那当然是行不通的
because a mock by definition is an empty
因为根据定义模拟是空的
object to provide stubs it provides
提供它提供的存根的对象
sorry it provides default values Knolls
抱歉，它提供了默认值
and zeros and false right it just
零和假对吧
refines it provides as little as it can
完善它提供的功能
and it's basically an empty husk it's
这基本上是一个空壳
gonna it'll help us get past the
它将帮助我们超越
construction phase here but if we need
施工阶段在这里，但如果我们需要
to do anything more than have a stand-in
除了站稳脚跟，还能做更多的事情
just to take up space and and get past
只是为了占据空间并过去
an occasional a certain old kolben
偶然的某个老科本
that's not gonna work what we need is a
那是行不通的，我们需要的是
stub a stub is a mock that has
存根是一个具有
pre-programmed behavior so here we're
预先设定的行为，所以我们在这里
gonna go back to our
回到我们的身边
raishin rest controller test and we're
赖信休息控制器测试，我们
gonna say Marketo ma ki toh dot when
要说Marketo ma ki toh dot when
this dot reservation pause did I find
我发现这个点保留暂停
all then returned collections dot
然后所有返回的集合点
singleton singleton list new reservation
单身人士单身人士清单新预订
so here it's gonna be one L and Jane
所以这里是L和Jane
right so we've got you know we're going
对，所以我们让您知道我们要去
to pre program it with an empty almost
预编程几乎是空的
empty list or just with one value and
空列表或仅包含一个值，并且
I'm gonna run that test again alright so
我要再次运行该测试，所以
there you go that you can see that that
你去那里，你可以看到
works
作品
we actually got back there's response
我们实际上回到了那里
that we're expecting the content type is
我们期望的内容类型是
equal to or compatible with applications
等于或与应用程序兼容
days and utf-8 and our application is
天和utf-8，我们的应用程序是
now fully tested so if we go to the
现在已经过全面测试，所以如果我们去
command line CD downloads beautiful
命令行CD下载精美
testing may even clean package you can
测试甚至可以清洁包装
see that the tests are fast they're
看到测试很快
cleaning the beam and we should have now
清洁光束，我们应该现在
a working
工作
Springwood application now the concepts
Springwood应用程序现在的概念
that we've looked at here are the
我们在这里看过的是
foundations upon which concepts like
诸如此类的概念的基础
consumer-driven contract testing rest
消费者驱动的合同测试休息
and we've looked at that at least a
而且我们至少已经看过
little bit we look look to that in some
我们期待一些
at some length in an earlier
在更早的时候
installation of spring tips where we
我们在哪里安装弹簧头
looked at spring cloud contract and had
看着春天的云合约，
support for mocking out HTTP services
支持模拟HTTP服务
there's more to discuss there we could
还有更多可以讨论的地方
talk about messaging and for example
谈论消息传递，例如
this also leads us very nicely into
这也使我们很好地进入
another discussion of j unit 5 so J
关于j单元5的另一个讨论
naught 5 of course is a different
零5当然是不同的
programming model it's not backwards
编程模型，它不向后
compatibility it's not it's not very
兼容性不是，不是很好
backwards compatible that said it's easy
向后兼容，说很容易
enough to get to move code to it and it
足以将代码移至其中
is a very very powerful paradigm it
是一个非常非常强大的范例
gives us a lot of benefits one of which
给我们带来很多好处，其中之一
of course is that I don't have to use on
当然是我不必使用
a wired private fields like this I can
这样的有线私人领域我可以
actually have constructor injection in
实际上有构造函数注入
my tests there's a number of other
我的测试还有很多其他的
things that are very compelling about it
令人信服的事情
and for the most part the spring testing
大部分是春季测试
apparatus works just as well we don't
仪器也一样好，我们不能
use they run with annotation anymore
使用它们与注释一起运行
that becomes an extension in Jane and
成为简的扩展，
five Jupiter world but it's something
五个木星世界，但是
worth looking into so the
值得研究，所以
perhaps that'll be the topic of another
也许那将是另一个话题
spring tips insulation at some point in
弹簧在某些时候提示绝缘
the future alright so with that my
未来还可以，所以我的
friends thanks so much for watching and
朋友非常感谢您的观看和
we'll see you next time
下次见
you
您